Myungyeon (Chloe) Lee

Software engineer with three years of experience. Passionate about creating efficient websites with JavaScript, HTML/CSS. Seeking opportunities to contribute my technical skills and creativity to a forward-thinking team.

3420 Rio Bravo Drive, San Jose, CA +1 (408) 839-4646 chloe.artache@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

PwC — Associate, Digital Innovation Lab

July 2021 - September 2022 | Seoul, South Korea

The Digital Innovation Lab is an organization that develops and operates digital products and business automation within PwC Korea.

- Developed and managed in-house automation tools, enhancing efficiency.
- Created user-friendly front-end services for complex audit report formats, featuring radio buttons, checkboxes, and dropdown selections.
- Automated tax questionnaire organization and analysis using PDFMiner, significantly increasing the tax team's efficiency.
- Consulted with clients about developing, auditing, and preparing security features for new forms of cryptocurrency.

Ziontech Solutions Inc. — Intern, Software Engineer

January 2020 - December 2020 | Milpitas, CA

ZionTech Solutions is a company that creates efficient human resource management software.

- Human resource solution, **Wavity** (https://www.wavity.com)
- Developed the Wavity website using Angular and Node.js.
- Reduced website load-times by minimizing HTTP requests and determining which queries were really needed.

Childly — Software Engineer

November 2019 - January 2020 | Seoul, South Korea Childly is a company that runs cryptocurrency exchange and studies cryptocurrency.

- Cryptocurrency exchange website, **BTX** (https://btxpro.co.kr)
- Developed the Dove Wallet website using Vue.js, Node.js.
- Gained expertise in cryptocurrency exchange platforms.

Knowru — Intern, Software Engineer

March 2019 - September 2019 | Seoul, South Korea

Knowru is a company that sells various B2B software that uses machine learning and AI in the USA, UK, and China.

- **Knowru** website (https://www.knowru.com)
- Developed the AI interview website (service is closed), Vue.js (Vuex), and the AWS serverless service.
- Manipulated AWS lambda functions with Python to manage APIs.

EDUCATION

Sogang University

2015 – 2021 | Seoul, South Korea Computer Science and Engineering

- Bachelor's Degree

SELECTED COURSES

Design and Analysis of Algorithm

Data Structures

Programming Languages

Advanced Software Practices

Java Programming

Operating Systems

Machine Learning Programming

SKILLS

React.js

Vue.js

Angular

Spring Boot

JavaScript

C

C++

Python

HTML/CSS

Git

LANGUAGE

Korean

English